beyond.ca 2013-10-17

# AOL.ca - Privacy Policy

| 

|  AOL is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that kids' information is protected. 

While this privacy policy applies to the AOL.CA site and all of the other Internet- 

---|---  
accessible AOL-branded services, like AOL Instant Messenger, we will refer here only to AOL.CA to make reading this policy easier. The AOL Internet online service has a separate privacy policy for its members. If you are an AOL member, you can find that policy within our Terms of Service. The purpose of this AOL.CA privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to AOL.CA, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit AOL.CA, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to AOL.CA and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked AOL.CA with our logo so you know where this policy applies.   
  
**Information About All AOL.CA Visitors**  
In general, our service automatically gathers certain "ratings" information when a visitor comes to AOL.CA. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, AOL.CA uses a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or E-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our AOL.CA partners about how our members, collectively, use AOL.CA. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well. 

**Information About You**  
Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service, like AOL Instant Messenger, or when you order a product. We will need certain information in order to provide that service or product to you and may also use that information to offer you additional products and services about which you might be interested. We may ask you for interest information so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to respond or not. Additionally, we may provide you with an opportunity to be listed in a directory on one of our AOL-branded services — these listings are also optional and you can make changes to or eliminate this information when you want to. 

**Third-party Advertising/Networks**  
We use third-party advertising companies and networks to serve ads. These third-party ad network providers may use web beacons and cookies to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, using non-personally identifiable data (such as sites visited and browser type) gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. If you would like more information about this practice, as well as your choices about not having this information used for online behavioral advertising by these ad networks, click here: <http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

**Disclosure**  
We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to AOL.CA or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, E-mail address or telephone number, to any outside companies. But as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of AOL.CA. 

**Special Attention to Kids**  
AOL takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of young people using our services. We do not specifically collect information about children and believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child's experience in cyberspace and to review our important safety tips before your child explores the Internet. We also encourage you and your child to visit AOL.CA's Kids Only Web Channel, which provides access to age-appropriate content available on the Web. AOL also recommends that parents who are AOL members use AOL's Parental Controls or, if not, other Web filtering technology to supervise their kids' access to the Web. 

**AOL.CA Privacy Policy Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy for AOL.CA, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

**Director of Privacy**  
Please direct all inquiries about our privacy policy for AOL.CA in writing to our designated Director of Privacy, AOL Canada Inc., 55 St. Clair Avenue East, Suite 700, Toronto, Ontario M4V 2Y7 or by fax to (416) 960 6560 or via e-mail: CAPrivacyinfo@aol.com. 

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---  
|  |  How to Get In Touch With Us |   
|  |   
**Member Services:**

1-800-AOL-HELP  

|   
|  |   
  
**AOL Canada Inc. Headquarters:**  
99 Spadina Avenue   
Suite 200   
Toronto, Ontario  
M5V 3P8   
Phone: (416) 263-8100  
Fax: (416) 263-8102  
  
|   
|  |   
  
Have Questions?  
Call toll free,  
**1-888-265-HELP** (4357)  
|   
---|---
